{
    "subject": "resource/Barbara_Robinson_(author)",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Barbara Robinson",
    "human_readable": "The full name of Barbara Robinson (author) is Barbara Robinson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9839774966239929,
            "question": "Is Barbara Robinson an author?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9808159470558167,
            "question": "What is the full name of Barbara Robinson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9396743178367615,
            "question": "Who is Barbara Robinson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9325762987136841,
            "question": "Is there a famous book written by Barbara Robinson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.91508948802948,
            "question": "What is the last name of Barbara Robinson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8821025490760803,
            "question": "What is the first name of Barbara Robinson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7804320454597473,
            "question": "What kind of books does Barbara Robinson write?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7548990249633789,
            "question": "What do we know about Barbara Robinson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5119243860244751,
            "question": "How can you find more information about Barbara Robinson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4768994152545929,
            "question": "Can you tell me anything else about Barbara Robinson?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The full name of Barbara Robinson (author) is Barbara Robinson.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6901_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How can you find more information about Barbara Robinson?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6901_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What do we know about Barbara Robinson?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6901_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of books does Barbara Robinson write?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6901_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6901_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6901_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6901_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6901_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6901_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6901_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6901_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6901_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6901_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6901_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation:\n\nSince there are multiple documents mentioning Barbara Robinson, I will check each one to see if it mentions her full name.\n\nDocument 1:\nBarbara Robinson Bio\n...this document doesn't mention her middle name, so we can't confirm whether \"Robinson\" is indeed her full last name. The output should be {'output': 'no'}.\n\n\nDocument 2:\nMEET THE AUTHOR\nBARBARA ROBINSON\n...\nThis document also only mentions her first name as Barbara Robinson, and doesn't provide any information about a middle name or further details of the surname \"Robinson\". We can't confirm whether this is indeed her full last name. The output should be {'output': 'no'}.\n\n\nDocument 3:\nBarbara Robinson is a wife, mother, author and retired public sector executive.\n...\nThis document doesn't mention Barbara's full name either.\n\nDocument 4:\nBarbara Robinson is an author of contemporary and historical romance set against a backdrop of magical realism.\n...\nSimilarly, this document only mentions her first name \"Barbara\".\n\n\nDocument 5:\nBarbara Robinson, author of the now-classic children's novel The Best Christmas Pageant Ever (Harper, 1972), died on July 9, 2013. \n...\nAnd neither does this document.\n\nDocument 6:\nBarbara Robinson, author of the long popular The Best Christmas Pageant Ever, published by HarperColllins in 1972, died on July 9,2013.\n...\nThis document is similar to Document 5.\n\n\nSince none of these documents provide information about Barbara's full last name, we can't confirm whether \"Robinson\" is indeed her full surname. Therefore the output should be {'output': 'no'}."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide various biographical details about Barbara Robinson, confirming that her full name is indeed Barbara Robinson and she was an author."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "I am not told Barbara Robinson's full name as \"Barbara Robinson\" but rather provided with various context information that includes different names and dates of birth, leading me to infer that the name \"Barbara Robinson\" might be a shortened or commonly used version of her actual full name.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}